All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwits special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now, they return to the Saba Odi Archipelago and move forward to the next stage of their journey, the New World.
Let nothing stop you from reaching the top!
Listen up, guys!
There's a lot I want to say, but we don't have much time.
One thing can't wait, though.
What you went through these past two years was selfish of me, so thanks for putting up with it.
Let's go!
The Man Who Guarded the Sunny
Brother, it's too hard to dig here!
Of course it is!
This island is all rocks and tree roots.
No, don't bury us!
We're victims too!
Please, I'll do anything you want!
Just let me live!
Captain Luffy!
No, I mean Black!
He made us do this!
Listen, I have a secret to share with you.
We didn't give a damn about going to the New World with the Straw Hats.
The reason we joined was so we could stab them in the back and collect their bounties without
them ever suspecting a thing.
No!
Drift!
Stop it!
I don't know what that goopy stuff is, but you're going to kill him if you keep that up!
I won't let my friend die!
Got him!
Take that, bastard!
Uh-oh.
That's weird.
Whoa!
And sure, your straw hat did look a little off, but it had been two years, so I didn't think
much of it.
You lied without remorse, and deception is a sin, one that you will be buried for.
Brother, how goes the grave?
I'm digging!
Sinners all, these poor fools.
Gods in heaven.
Please, forgive them.
Grant them peace and death.
Yes!
No!
Peace, yes, but not death!
Still, it's not all bad, I suppose.
I did find the real Luffy.
Hehehehehe!
I told you there wasn't any choice in the matter.
What did you expect?
Dark King Rayleigh was there.
He's as strong as Kizalu.
Even with the pacifistas, we couldn't so much as slow him down.
Unfortunately, the Caribou Brothers escaped along with the rest of their crew.
It seems they took some of the fake straw hats with them as well, though I can't imagine
why.
At any rate, we captured most of the pirates, even though the real straw hats heavily
damaged two of our pacifistas.
One of the units was the same prototype they fought before.
Its strength hasn't changed in the last two years.
That's bad news for us.
I don't know what they've been up to, but the straw hats are immeasurably more dangerous
than before.
Tell the Marines in the New World that they have a new threat coming their way.
The straw hats have returned, and they're stronger than we could have imagined.
A pity they had to take off so soon.
But I'm proud of them.
They're tough.
They're gonna do just fine.
You were watching?
Yes.
I'm a big fan.
I know that smile, Ray.
What's on your mind?
Huh?
Ah.
It's nothing, really.
Whoa-ho-ho!
Huh?
Hey, that's a nice ship you got there.
Thanks, but it's not exactly mine.
Rather, I stole it after my house burned down.
Oh, yeah?
And what's your name?
Rayleigh.
My name's Roger.
It's destiny meeting you, I say.
Oh, yeah?
How about we team up and turn this whole world upside down?
Huh?
And I thought I drank too much.
I don't know who you are or what you're selling, but I'm not interested.
Come on, you got a good thing going here.
Your ship might be small, but if we handle it right, I bet it could even survive a storm.
We could conquer the seas in this thing.
Let's set sail!
What do you mean, we?
I just met you half a minute ago.
Why don't you get your own damn boat?
One of these days, you're going to look back at this and realize it was the beginning of the greatest adventure ever known.
Before then, I never believed much in fate, but maybe nothing really happens by accident.
We're just too blind to see all the signs.
Anyway, that hat found the right man.
So long as it sails, I'll stay here, waiting.
Because I want to see a new king before I die.
The surface is already so far away.
What a view!
I've been under before, but portholes on a submarine?
They got nothing on this!
We're sinking!
Sinking!
What if we get a leak?
This is freaking me out!
Yeah, it feels like we're leaving the whole world behind.
It's eerie.
No big deal.
I've done this like a bajillion times before.
It's cool.
Nope, not pooping my pants at all here.
The ocean sure is awesome!
Look at that!
They really are trees, huh?
Wow, I totally forgot about that!
They're giant mangroves.
You can't tell when you're up top, but it's sure quite a sight to see from down here.
The majesty of nature is truly humbling!
Why, my eyes would be popping out of my skull if I had any eyes to speak of, I mean.
Who cares?
I've seen this.
Because you got on the wrong ship!
Shut up!
Don't ruin this for us!
These roots, they're beautiful.
And think about it.
They stretch all the way down to the bottom of the sea.
Okay, you win.
Hey, Chopper, I think there's something behind that tree.
Huh?
Whoa!
It's huge!
Took us long enough to get here.
But whatever, it was worth the wait.
I wonder what comes next.
Oh, fishies!
Huh?
Then I can grab them!
I see.
These look pretty good, too.
Here goes.
That's not funny!
If you put that bubble in, we'll die!
I'm gonna kill you!
Twice!
Nami, you know how the coding works, right?
Can we get some basic tips before another idiot flips out on us?
Good point.
Okay.
Rayleigh gave me a manual, but I can summarize it.
So, listen closely, okay?
She's real!
I can die happy!
Saatchi!
You don't have to take us with you!
Who's flipping out now, idiot?
What?
His nosebleed shot out!
I see.
It maintains its shape well.
You'd think that it would burst,
especially considering the immense amount of water pressure the coding must be exposed to.
How nice.
And I thought we'd all drown down here, never to be seen again.
Saatchi!
Get out of the ocean!
Bright seawater!
Damn it!
Keep pulling!
Saatchi!
What the heck happened to you back there?
I knew you were weak to pretty girls, but this is a real liability!
You're supposed to be cool!
That poor man.
I can only imagine the horrors he must have endured during the past two years.
Let's hope he lives long enough to see the mermaids he was so looking forward to.
And let's also hope they aren't quite so lovely that the sight of them strikes him dead.
When we get there, we'll have to ask for blood donations, but they won't be human.
I hope fishmen have the same kind of blood as him.
So, Sunny's coding has the same properties as the bubbles on Saba-Odi, meaning that objects or people can pass in and out without causing it any harm at all.
Spare me the bubble science!
We got a man down here!
Sanji aside, she's not wrong.
We saw this all over Saba-Odi.
It only stretches so far, then allows an object to pass through.
So, the good news is, if we get attacked by any nasty sea creatures, we can still fire cannons at them, just like we would if we were above water.
Huh?
Wait, so what would pop it? Is it that durable?
It does fine with single objects, but if too many things pass through at once, then it'll break.
Let's see, like if a sea king clamps down on the ship, for example. That's bad.
We're safe. Good riddance.
Also, the coating doesn't protect the ship from anything except water.
So, if we crash into a rock or a trench and the mast breaks or something like that, then the bubble could also burst.
So, it's not like we can just bounce around down here.
Still, as long as we take the usual precautions, we should be fine.
I mean, I'm sure Luffy will try to get us all killed, but what else is new?
So, we're in the clear after all. Good!
Well, in theory at least, but a lot of ships try to make the trip to Fishman Island, and over 70% of them sink.
We are so dead!
One gum gum gatling, and I bet I can catch all the fish swimming out there.
Yeah, if I cut enough holes in this bubble thing, I bet I could catch even more.
Aren't you listening to Nami?
That's too many holes! Our chances down here are bad enough as it is!
Oh, break your bones! Let's fix them! Let's break them again!
No fair! Haji said he'd show us the Fishman Island like it was no big deal, and now we're stuck in this death bubble slowly descending to our demise!
Oh, yeah! Lunchtime! They packed a bunch of food for me! Since Sanji's sick, we should have ourselves a Pikmin!
Yay! All that screaming made me hungry!
And I'm wasting away! Cool! As long as Nami thinks the ship will stay stable. We don't have to steer it or anything right now, do we?
Nope. We'll just be cruising on the sea current till we get further down. So, yeah. I'm sure we'll have more excitement a bit later, but for the time being, we might as well just kick back and take it easy.
Well, I wouldn't call this taking it easy exactly, but there's something you guys should probably know before we reach Fishman Island.
Now, this is a little heavy, so I hope it doesn't ruin lunch for everybody.
I think I know. I'm ready.
It's robot stuff, Bryce! You've got all kinds of secrets, don't you?
Can you transform into a tank? Or wait, maybe?
You've got laser guns!
Tell us, Robo-Bro!
Super armored!
Me.
Sorry, no new secrets. Secrets inaccessible, Robo.
He speaks robot!
Okay, I know robots are cool, but listen up. Or eat and listen if you like.
Like Usopp said, Hachi was supposed to show us the way to Fishman Island himself, but he got hurt real bad back on Saba Odi.
He came down here ahead of us to get medical treatment.
Anyway, it was the same thing that happened to Duval.
Meaning, he was protecting the Sunny from anyone who came for it.
Things got ugly about a year ago when the Navy found out the ship was docked there.
Both him and Duval got taken out in a big fight.
Huh? Wait, a year? Then who was protecting the Sunny after that?
We had one more secret ally.
If not really, then who?
Someone who separated us two years ago, for better or worse. The Warlord.
Huh?
Turns out Bartholomew Kuma was on our side the whole time.
A few days back, when I made it to the Sunny, I couldn't believe my eyes.
He was right there.
I've been waiting for you.
What the hell are you doing here?
Mission accomplished.
You saw for yourself. There wasn't a single scratch on the Sunny.
Later, Rayleigh gave me the whole story.
I am a member of the Revolutionary Army.
If it's within my power, I want to help the Straw Hats escape from here.
You guys probably knew that something was up, but now we know the truth.
He saved the Sunny, and he saved our lives.
And then, after we were sent flying from the island,
Kuma paid Rayleigh a visit and dropped another bombshell.
I don't have much time. Not as myself.
The details are a little sketchy, but evidently, Kuma surrendered his body to the Navy.
They used him as an experiment and replaced his body parts one by one.
By the time the War of the Best rolled around, his personality had been completely erased.
Wait. He knew where he sent us, but he didn't know what we'd do once we got there, or that we would even make it back.
And you said his personality was taken away, but he still protected the Sunny?
The guy who worked on him is this dude named Dr. Vegapunk, and Kuma must have made a deal with him,
because he programmed one final mission into his brain.
Defend the Thousand Sunny from any attackers until the moment that a Straw Hat returns to claim it.
So even though he's been reduced to a living weapon with no memory,
he's been carrying out his own orders, protecting our ship for the past two years to fulfill his last wish.
But why? He barely knew us. I mean, why'd it matter to him?
I don't know. Maybe it's cause of Luffy.
You said Kuma was part of the Revolutionary Army, and Luffy's dad was the leader of those guys, right?
I don't know much about my dad, but it seems like that robot bear dude was a good guy,
so we can't be too bad if they're friends.
Kuma...
The bottom line is, our survival and all the things we accomplished in the past two years we owe to him.
Whatever his reason was, we should be grateful.
And we may never find out the truth, because it's not like we can ask him to explain himself anymore.
All we can do now is honor his memory, and know that Bartholomew Kuma was our greatest ally,
until he took his last breath as a human.
Unfortunately, we'll never be able to thank him, since he'll just be a weapon, and likely our enemy the next time we meet.
That's all I wanted to say.
Kind of a lot to work through all at once, isn't it? Someday. I hope we can at least find out the rest of the story.
Kuma saved us, huh?
Oh, you're awake. Good.
Have some lunch! It's from Amazon Lily.
Oh, Amazon Lily. The island with all the women.
Of course that's where he sent you. Do you know where I was these past two years?
Because I'm kinda thinking Kuma's not such a good friend after all. In fact, if he were here right now, I'd like to kick his metal face in!
Now, now, Sanji. We've all had our share of troubles. Before I became a pop music sensation, I was trapped in a cage. Still, the only thing that matters now is the voyage awaiting us.
You don't know, man! You don't know anything!
Straight ahead! Brother! Look! It's them!
I know! Like you said, they're straight ahead. You think I'm blind? Looks like we'll be sailing with the Straw Hats after all.
Well, how far down are we?
I don't know, but it's getting darker and darker.
We passed the photic zone, and it looks like we're around the bottom of the aphotic zone. About a thousand meters, give or take.
It's quiet, and the sunny itself feels oddly still. It's almost like floating in the sky.
The sky. I learned so much about weather up there, but I don't know if it's much use under water.
Hey, look! It's a whale!
It's just like Laboon!
Nah, it looks more like Whitebeard.
I can't think about whales right now. I can't think about anything except the fact that I'm going to die. Or at least 70% going to die.
Why did they tell me that? Maybe if I keep a lookout, I can raise our chances of making it out of this.
Better than just sitting here. I don't see any big scary sea kings or stuff the ship could crash into. So I guess we're good for now.
Wait a sec. What is that thing? A fish? No.
Are you ready? We only get one shot at this!
Ready, brother!
Ready, Captain!
Before you say anything, I know what you're thinking.
Just shoot them, and they'll all drown.
They're wanted dead or alive after all, so why not let them die?
Well, that wouldn't do at all, because the Navy wouldn't know who killed them.
We have to deliver their heads personally on a silver platter. Then they will fear us!
The whole world will know our strength!
We'll take them out before they suspect a thing!
My big smiling face is the last thing they'll see before they die!
Yes, sir! Uh, right, yeah!
Hey, you guys, there's a ship-looking thing coming our way!
What?
You sure?
Why don't you come look for yourself?
Charge!
It's a pirate ship!
They're ramming straight into us!
Go away, you morons! You're gonna make us all drown!
They're not trying to break our ship! They're trying to board it!
Damn it! Who are they?
The Suni continues descending towards Fishman Island now with a decidedly unwelcome caribou on board.
With their bubble threatening to pop at every turn, the crew braves an undersea waterfall only to stumble into the den of the legendary monster, the Kraken.
With no way to battle such a massive foe, a watery grave seems all but inevitable.
On the next One Piece, deadly combat under the sea, the demon of the ocean strikes!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!